LATEST COVID-19 UPDATE

LATEST COVID-19 UPDATE

Close

Welcome to the

!

Please enjoy our special offers for you

[Search](javascript:void(0)) [Open Menu](javascript:void(0))

*   [Mobile](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Featured](javascript:void(0))
        
        *   [Galaxy Note20 | 20 Ultra 5G  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/smartphones/galaxy-note20/)
        *   [Galaxy Z Fold2 5G  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/smartphones/galaxy-z-fold2/)
        *   [Galaxy Watch3  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/watches/all-watches/)
        *   [Galaxy Buds Live  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/audio-sound/galaxy-buds/galaxy-buds-live-mystic-bronze-sm-r180nznaeua/)
        *   [Galaxy Tab S7 | S7+  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/tablets/galaxy-tab-s/galaxy-tab-s7-plus-12-4-inch-mystic-bronze-128gb-5g-sm-t976bznaeua/)
        
    *   [Smartphones](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Tablets](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Watches](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Audio](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Accessories](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Apps & Services](javascript:void(0))

    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))
    
*   [TV & AV](javascript:void(0))

    **TV & AV**
    
    *   [Featured](javascript:void(0))

    *   [TVs](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Lifestyle TVs](javascript:void(0))

    *   [TV by Size](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Sound Devices](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Business TVs](javascript:void(0))

     [25% Cashback on soundbars or 50% when bought with a TV
    
    Learn more](https://www.samsung.com/ie/offer/samsung-soundbar-cashback-offer/)
    
    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))
    
*   [Home Appliances](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Featured](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Refrigerators](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Laundry](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Cooking Appliances](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Dishwashers](javascript:void(0))

    *   Smart Ways to Shop
    
     [All new Samsung energy efficient washing machines and dryers
    
    Learn more](https://www.samsung.com/ie/washers-and-dryers/ecobubble-smart-control/)
    
    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))
    
*   [Computing](javascript:void(0))

    **Computing**
    
    *   [Featured](javascript:void(0))

    *   [IT](javascript:void(0))
        
        *   [Memory & Storage  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/memory-storage/)
        
    *   [Galaxy Book](javascript:void(0))
        
        *   [Galaxy Book S Intel  
            ](https://www.samsung.com/ie/pc/galaxy-book/galaxy-book-s-intel-i5-8gb-512gb-np767xcm-k02uk/)

     [Super Fast External Storage
    
    Learn more](https://www.samsung.com/ie/memory-storage/portable-ssd/)
    
    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))
    
*   [Shop](javascript:void(0))

    **Shop**
    
    *   [Smart Ways to Buy](javascript:void(0))

    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))

*   [Explore](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Stories](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Brand](javascript:void(0))

     [Nothing in Between
    
    Learn more](https://www.samsung.com/ie/explore/brand/nothing-in-between/)
    
    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))
    
*   [Support](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Product page](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Solutions & Tips](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Repair Service](javascript:void(0))

    *   [Contact](javascript:void(0))

     [Useful guide to use Galaxy S20 series
    
    Learn more](https://www.samsung.com/ie/support/useful-guide-to-use-galaxy-s20-series/)
    
    [Close Menu](javascript:void(0))

*   [Search](javascript:void(0))

[Close Menu](javascript:void(0))

[OK](javascript:void(0) "No Access OK")

No Access Close

[OK](javascript:void(0);)

Layer Popup Close

Your cart is empty.

Layer Popup Close

Sorry, there is insufficient stock for your cart.

Layer Popup Close

Remove a Product
----------------

Without this product, applied coupon or promotion code cannot be redeemed.  
Are you sure to remove this product?

Layer Popup Close

Privacy Policy
--------------

 I have read and agree to the Samsung.com [Privacy Policy](https://www.samsung.com/ie/info/privacy/ "Open in a New Window") 

Tick this box to proceed to Samsung.com.

  By ticking this box, I accept Samsung Service Updates, including :

Samsung.com Services and marketing information, new product and service announcements as well as special offers, events and newsletters.

Close Privacy Policy

Check Preferences
-----------------

Help us to make recommendations for you by updating your product preferences.

[YES](javascript:void(0);)

[LATER](javascript:void(0);)

Close Check Preferences

Can we help find anything?
--------------------------

Search form

Close  Galaxy Note20   Cancel   Search 

Suggested Searches

NO SUGGESTIONS

Search History

Clear All

Related Searches

Matched Contents

Galaxy Note20 Galaxy S20 Galaxy A51 QLED 8K TV 98 inch QLED TV QuickDrive Washing Machine One Door Refrigerator

Cancel

PRIVACY
=======

Privacy
-------

SAMSUNG PRIVACY POLICY HIGHLIGHTS
---------------------------------

Samsung Electronics knows how important privacy is to our customers. We want to make sure you understand how we collect and use your personal information across all of our Samsung devices and services, from mobile phones and tablets to TVs, home appliances, online services, and more.

While this Privacy Policy applies to all our services, we’ll also provide additional information about privacy related to particular services where necessary.

OVERVIEW OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
--------------------------------

We collect personal information that you provide directly, information about how you use our services and information from third party sources. We use this information to provide you with services, understand the way you use our services so we can improve and personalise your experience and to develop the most relevant apps, technologies, and content for our customers. We also use personal information to provide customised advertising tailored to your interests.

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
---------------------------------

We may share your personal information with affiliate companies of Samsung Electronics, as well as with companies that provide services on behalf of Samsung Electronics. We may also share your personal information with trusted partner companies, such as mobile service providers or insurance companies, that provide you with products and services that you request and information about products and services you may be interested in. We share personal information with law enforcement agencies when it’s required by law or to protect Samsung Electronics and its users.

*   ### [GENERAL PRIVACY POLICY](javascript:void(0))
    
    _Effective Date: 26th October, 2020_
    
    This Privacy Policy applies to all of our Samsung devices and services, from mobile phones and tablets to TVs, home appliances, online services, and more, collectively called Services.
    
    It’s important that you check back often for updates to the Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy periodically to reflect changes in our personal information practices with respect to the Services or changes in applicable law. We’ll post a notice on our website or on your device to notify you in advance of material changes to our Privacy Policy and indicate at the top of the Privacy Policy when it was most recently updated. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will always be available here: [https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp](https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp). In addition to this Privacy Policy, Samsung may also provide specific privacy notices related to certain products and services. In the event of any deviation between the terms of this Privacy Policy and a specific privacy notice, the terms of the specific privacy notice control.
    
*   ### [WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?](javascript:void(0))
    
    Samsung Electronics collects your personal information in a variety of ways.

    _Information You Provide Directly_
    
    Some Services enable you to give us information directly. For example:
    
    *   When you create an account or profile with us, we may ask for information such as your name, date of birth, or email address.
    *   If you order a product or paid service from us, we may ask for your name, address, contact information, and shipping and payment information to process your order.
    *   To provide responses when you contact Customer Service, we may need information to verify your identify and the product you’re inquiring about.
    *   When you communicate with our Customer Service staff or others, your communications will be transmitted through our systems.
    *   If you share your contacts, we’ll collect their phone numbers and other contact information to facilitate file sharing and messaging. You can turn off or restrict these features in Settings on your devices.

    _Information About Your Use of Services_
    
    In addition to the information you provide, we will collect information about your use of our Services through software on your devices and by other means. We will collect:
    
    *   **Device information** Your hardware model, device hardware information, IMEI number and other unique device identifiers, phone number, serial number, sales code, access recording, current software version, MCC (Mobile Country Code), MNC (Mobile Network Code), MAC address, IP address, cookies, pixels, subscription information, operating system versions, and settings of the devices you use to access Services.
    *   **Log information** Diagnostic, technical, error, and usage information such as the time and duration of your use of Services, search query terms when you enter search terms into your device in connection with a particular Samsung Service, and any information stored in cookies that we have set on your devices.
    *   **Location information** Your device’s GPS signal or information about nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers that may be transmitted to us when you use certain Services and enable the Location function.
    *   **Voice information** Recordings of your voice that we make and store on our servers when you enable this function and use voice commands to control a Service, or when you contact our Customer Service team. Note that if we work with a third party service provider that provides speech-to-text conversion services on our behalf, this provider may receive and store certain voice commands in accordance with the contract concluded between us and our trusted third-party service provider.
    *   **Samsung Keyboard information** The words that you type when you enable Predictive text. This feature may be offered in connection with your Samsung account to synchronise the data for use on your other Samsung mobile devices. You can clear the data by going to the Predictive text settings.
    *   **Viewing Information** The networks, channels, websites visited, and programs viewed on your devices and the amount of time spent viewing them.
    *   Other information about your use of Services, such as the apps you use, the websites you visit, and how you interact with content offered through a Service.

    _Publicly or Commercially Available or Shared Information_
    
    We sometimes gather publicly or commercially available information, including information from social networks you use, and combine this with other information about you so that we can better understand your needs, interests, and preferences. We also sometimes gather information about you when other people provide it using our Services, such as your name and contact information when others send a message to you or share files with you.

    _Other Information We Collect_
    
    We may also collect other information about you, your devices, or your use of Services that you consent to send us.

    _Third Party Analytics_
    
    Through certain Services, we may collect personal information about your online activities on websites and connected devices over time and across third-party websites, devices, apps and other online features and services. We may use third-party analytics services on the Services, such as those of Google Analytics. The service providers that administer these analytics services help us to analyse your use of the Services and improve the Services. The information we obtain may be disclosed to or collected directly by these providers and other relevant third parties who use the information, for example, to evaluate use of the Services, help administer the Services and diagnose technical issues. To learn more about Google Analytics, please visit [http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

    _Your Options_
    
    You can choose not to provide us with certain types of information, such as information requested as part of registering a Samsung account. In some cases, this may limit your ability to use some Services. We’ll do our best to explain these limitations when we’re asking for your information so you can make an informed decision. For example, Samsung Cloud allows you to back up your information and create a restore point; however, Samsung Cloud was not designed nor intended to store or process sensitive information.
    
*   ### [HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?](javascript:void(0))
    
    _We use the information we collect for the following purposes:_
    
    *   To help you or your device register for our Services
    *   To provide a Service or feature you request
    *   To provide customised content and personalised services based on your past activities on our Services
    *   To provide customised advertising, promotions, and offers that might interest you on our websites, third-party websites, and online platforms such as social media sites
    *   To provide promotions and offers by way of direct marketing communications, only where you have given us your separate consent
    *   To analyse our products and services to help us better understand our customers in order to offer the most relevant communications, services, and experiences to you
    *   To ask you for your opinions on our products and services and to carry out customer surveys, with your separate consent if required
    *   To provide software updates, maintenance services, and support for your devices
    *   To comply with the law and legal processes
    *   To protect the rights, property, or safety of Samsung Electronics, or any of our affiliates, business partners, or customers
    
    We use and combine the information we collect about you from our Services, devices, or other sources to provide you with a better experience. For example, you can use your Samsung account details not only on the Service you registered with, but other Services which use Samsung accounts. We also use the information you provide directly or through other sources as described above to provide content you may like or that you’ve personalised.

    You have choices about your information. Check out the [WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?](#privacy-ctns-seven) section to learn more.

    \[For European Economic Area (EEA) Residents only\]

    Samsung processes personal information for the purposes described above. Samsung’s legal basis to process personal information includes processing:
    
    (i) So that we can keep our promises to you, such as providing you with a Service  
    (ii) To promote our business interests (for example, to manage our relationship with you and improve your customer service experience), including communications on our website, third party websites, and online platforms  
    (iii) To comply with the law and legal processes  
    (iv) With your consent (for example, to send direct marketing communications). If you give consent, you can always revoke by contacting us as specified in the [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section of this Privacy Policy.

    Samsung Electronics is the data controller of your personal information as described above. For some direct marketing communications and some customised advertising in Europe, Samsung Electronics (UK) Limited, which is located in the United Kingdom, is also the data controller of your personal information. Some of our European Samsung subsidiaries also process your personal information in their countries. Where applicable, the European Samsung subsidiary has its own local Privacy Policy on its website to explain this.
    
*   ### [WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?](javascript:void(0))
    
    We will disclose your information internally within our business, but only to those who need it to further provide Services or to help with your requests.
    
    We will also disclose your information to the following entities, only to the extent that this will be necessary to provide our Services:
    
    *   **Affiliates:** Other Samsung Electronics Group companies which we control or own.
    *   **Business Partners:** Partners who we work together with to provide you the Services you’ve requested or bought. For example, we may work with a bank so that you can use one of our Services to make faster and more efficient payments. These business partners control and manage your personal information.
    *   **Service Providers:** Carefully selected companies that provide services for or on behalf of us, such as companies that help us with repairs, customer contact centers, customer care activities, advertising (including customised advertising on our websites, third-party websites, or online platforms), conducting customer satisfaction surveys, or billing, or that send emails on our behalf. These providers are also committed to protecting your information.
    *   **Other Parties When Required by Law or as Necessary to Protect Our Services:** For example, it may be necessary by law, legal process, or court order from governmental authorities to disclose your information. They may also seek your information from us for the purposes of law enforcement, national security, anti-terrorism, or other issues that are related to public security.
    *   **Other Parties in Connection with Corporate Transactions:** We may disclose your information to a third party as part of a merger or transfer, acquisition or sale, or in the event of a bankruptcy.
    *   **Other Parties with Your Consent or at Your Direction:** In addition to the disclosures described in this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with third parties when you separately consent to or request such sharing.
    
*   ### [HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SECURE?](javascript:void(0))
    
    We take data protection seriously. We’ve put in place physical and technical safeguards to keep the information we collect secure. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, Internet transmission, computer system, or wireless connection is completely secure.
    
*   ### [WHERE DO WE SEND YOUR DATA?](javascript:void(0))
    
    Your use of our Services will involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information within and outside of your country of residence, consistent with this policy. In particular, your personal information will be transferred to the Republic of Korea. Please note that the data protection and other laws of countries to which your information may be transferred might not be as comprehensive as those in your country.

    \[For European Economic Area (EEA) Residents Only\]

    In addition, your use of the Services may also involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information to other countries; such countries include, without limitation, countries in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, the United States of America, China, Singapore, Vietnam, India, Canada, the Philippines, and Japan. We will take appropriate measures, in compliance with applicable law, to ensure that your personal information remains protected. Such measures include the use of Standard Contractual Clauses to safeguard the transfer of data outside of the EEA. To request more information or to obtain a copy of the contractual agreements in place, contact us. See the [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section.
    
*   ### [WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?](javascript:void(0))
    
    Your personal information belongs to you. You can ask us to provide details about what we’ve collected, and you can ask us to delete it or correct any inaccuracies. You can also ask us to restrict or limit processing, sharing, or transfer of your personal information, as well as to provide to you your personal information that we’ve collected so you can use it for your own purposes. However, requesting the deletion of your personal information may also result in a loss of access to Services we provide. We won’t delete data that we’re required by law to retain.

    To make a request concerning your rights or to make an inquiry, contact us. See the [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section.
    
*   ### [HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?](javascript:void(0))
    
    We won’t keep your personal information for longer than is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. This means that information will be destroyed or erased from our systems when it’s no longer required.

    We take appropriate steps to ensure that we process and retain information about you based on the following logic:

    1\. At least the duration for which the information is used to provide you with a service  
    2\. As required under law, a contract, or with regard to our statutory obligations  
    3\. Only for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, is processed, or longer if required under any contract, by applicable law, or for statistical purposes, subject to appropriate safeguards.
    
*   ### [WHAT THIRD-PARTY SERVICES DO WE USE?](javascript:void(0))
    
    Some of the content, advertising, and functionality in our Services is provided by third parties. These third parties may use cookies, beacons, tracking pixels, and other tools to collect information about your use of these Services. These third parties are not controlled directly by Samsung, so we recommend that you check their privacy policies to understand how they use your data.

    For some apps and services, including social networks, we receive and store sign-in information, as well as other information that you allow us to receive when you connect with these apps and services.
    
*   ### [COOKIES, BEACONS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES](javascript:void(0))
    
    We, as well as certain third parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality in our Services, use cookies, pixels, beacons, and other technologies in certain areas of our Services.

    **Cookies**
    
    Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, TV, mobile phone, or other device. They enable the entity that put the cookie on your device to recognize you across different websites, services, devices, and browsing sessions. Cookies serve many useful purposes. For example:
    
    *   Cookies can remember your sign-in credentials so you don’t have to enter those credentials each time you sign in to a service.
    *   Cookies help us and third parties understand which parts of our Services are the most popular because they help us to see which pages and features visitors are accessing and how much time they’re spending on the pages. Studying this information helps us to adapt the Services and provide you with a better experience.
    *   Cookies help us and third parties understand which ads you’ve seen so you don’t get the same ad each time you access a Service.
    *   Cookies help us and third parties to provide you with relevant content and advertising by collecting information about your use of our Services and other websites and apps.
    
    When you use a web browser to access Services, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the help menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Your device operating system may contain additional cookie controls. Note that some Services are designed to work using cookies, so disabling cookies may affect your ability to use those Services or certain parts of them.

    **Other Local Storage**
    
    We, along with certain third parties, may use other kinds of local storage technologies, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as Flash cookies) and HTML5 local storage, in connection with our Services. These technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above. They’re stored on your devices and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these technologies may make use of different parts of your devices from standard cookies, so you might not be able to control them using standard browser tools and settings. For information about disabling or deleting information contained in Local Shared Objects, visit [http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html).
    
    **Beacons**
    
    We, along with certain third parties, may use technologies called beacons or pixels that communicate information from your device to a server. Beacons can be embedded in online content, videos, and emails, and can allow a server to read certain types of information from your device, know when you’ve viewed particular content or a particular email message, and determine the time and date on which you viewed the beacon and the IP address of your device. We and certain third parties use beacons for a variety of purposes, including to analyze the use of our Services and, along with cookies, to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you.
    
*   ### [CONTACT US](javascript:void(0))
    
    You can contact us to update your preferences, correct your information, submit a request, or ask us questions.

    The easiest way is through the Contact Us section of [https://www.samsung.com/](https://www.samsung.com/).

    You can also contact us at:

    Data Controller  
    Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.  
    129, Samsung-ro, Yeongtong-gu,  
    Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do 16677, Republic of Korea

    \[For European Economic Area (EEA) Residents Only\]

    Samsung Electronics has offices across Europe, so we can ensure that your request or query will be handled by the data protection team based in your region.

    The easiest way to contact us is through our Privacy Support Page at [https://www.samsung.com/request-desk](https://www.samsung.com/request-desk/).

    You can also contact us at:

    European Data Protection Officer  
    Samsung Electronics (UK) Limited  
    Samsung House, 1000 Hillswood Drive, Chertsey, Surrey KT16 0PS  

    You can lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes applicable law. Contact details for all EU supervisory authorities can be found at [https://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item\_id=612080](https://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).
    
*   ### [PRIVACY POLICY FOR SAMSUNG ONLINE SHOP](javascript:void(0))
    
    **Privacy Policy of Samsung.com E-commerce Platform**
    
    Samsung Electronics, including its affiliate group companies, know how important privacy is to our customers. We want to make sure you understand how we collect and use your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use your personal information on Samsung.com, enabling us to provide this online sales platform (the “E-Commerce Platform”) and allowing you to browse and purchase our products. Different Samsung entities in the Samsung group of companies will collect and process your data for different purposes, in particular Samsung Samsung Electronics (UK) Ltd and Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd located in Korea (collectively “Samsung Electronics”).
    
    If you decide to use the Samsung Upgrade Programme, credit and/or insurance services via our E-Commerce Platform your personal data will be processed by partner companies who assist us in operating these services. The privacy policies of these companies will be made available to you at the point at which your personal data is provided to them.
    
    **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**
    
    Samsung Electronics collects your personal information in a variety of ways.
    
    Information You Provide Directly
    
    We collect information from you when you use our E-Commerce Platform. For example:
    
    *   When you sign in to our E-Commerce Platform using Samsung account we will receive access to information from your account such as your name or email address. If you order a product from us, we will collect your purchase details and will ask for your name, address, contact information and shipping information and method of payment to process your order.
    *   In order to provide responses to you when you contact customer service, we may need information to verify your identity and the product you are inquiring about.
    *   When you interact with our Customer Services staff, your communications will be transmitted through our systems.
    
    Information About Your Use of the E-Commerce Platform.
    
    In addition to the information you provide, we will collect information about your use of our E-Commerce Platform. We will collect:
    
    *   Information about the product you purchase – hardware model, IMEI number, serial number.
    *   Device information - IP address, cookies, beacons.
    *   Log information –any information stored in cookies that we have set on your device.
    *   Other information about your use of the E-Commerce Platform, including how you interact with content offered through the Platform.
    
    Third Party Analytics
    
    Through certain Services, we may collect personal information about your online activities on websites and connected devices over time and across third-party websites, devices, apps and other online features and services. We may use third-party analytics services on the Services, such as those of Google Analytics. The service providers that administer these analytics services help us to analyze your use of the Services and improve the Services. The information we obtain may be disclosed to or collected directly by these providers and other relevant third parties who use the information, for example, to evaluate use of the Services, help administer the Services and diagnose technical issues. To learn more about Google Analytics, please visit [http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
    
    Your Options
    
    You can choose not to provide us with certain types of information, such as information requested as part of registering a Samsung account. In some cases, this may limit your ability to use some services. We will do our best to explain these limitations when we are asking for your information so you can make an informed decision.
    
    **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**
    
    We will use the information we collect for the following purposes:
    
    *   to provide you with services, including the opportunity to enter into a sales agreement with the operator of the Samsung online store as well as options to trade in a device, take out insurance or obtain credit for the purchase;
    *   to provide customized content and provide personalized services based on your past activities on our E-Commerce Platform;
    *   to provide customized advertising, promotions, and offers on our website, third party websites, and online platforms (for example, a social media site) if we consider that you will be interested in them;
    *   to provide promotions and offers by way of direct marketing communications only where you have given us your separate consent
    *   to analyse our products and services to help us better understand more about our customers in order to offer the most relevant communications, services and experiences to you;
    *   to ask you for your opinions on our products and services and to carry out customer surveys with your separate consent if required;
    *   to comply with the law and legal process; and
    *   to protect the rights, property, or safety of Samsung, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, or customers.
    
    We use and combine the information we collect about you from our E-Commerce Platform, devices, or other lawful ways to provide you with a better experience. For example, you can use your Samsung account details not only on the E-Commerce Platform, but for other services which use Samsung account. We also use the information you provide directly or through other sources as described above to provide content you may like or that you have personalized to your specific taste. Sometimes, you may have choices regarding your information. Check out the [**WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?**](#privacy-ctns-seven) section to learn more.
    
    Samsung processes personal information for the purposes described above. Samsung’s legal basis to process personal information includes processing:
    
    *   so that we can keep our promise to you, such as providing you with the E-Commerce Platform;
    *   to promote our business interests, for example, to manage our relationship with you and improve your customer service experience, including communications on our website, third party websites, and online platforms;
    *   to comply with law and legal process; and
    *   with your consent, for example to provide direct marketing communications. However, if you give consent, you can always revoke this by contacting us as specified in the [**CONTACT US**](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section of this Privacy Policy.
    
    **WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?**
    
    We will disclose your information internally within our business, but only to those who need it to further provide you with services or to help with your request.
    
    We will also disclose your information to the following entities, only to the extent that this will be necessary to perform our services:
    
    *   Affiliates. Other Samsung Electronics Group companies we control or own.
    *   Business Partners. Partners who we work together with to provide you the services you have requested or opted to buy. These business partners control and manage your personal information, including the partner who provides our trade in option. They will have their own privacy policies which set out details of how they use your personal data.
    *   Service Providers. Carefully selected companies that provide services for or on behalf of us, such as companies that help us with repairs, customer contact centers, customer care activities, financial services, advertising, including customized advertising on our website, third party websites, or online platforms, conducting customer satisfaction surveys, billing, or that send emails on our behalf. These providers are also committed to protecting your information.
    *   Other Parties when required by law or as necessary to protect our services. There may be instances when we disclose your information to other parties. For example, it may be necessary by law and legal process, or by other court order from governmental authorities to disclose your information. They may also seek your information from us for the purpose of law enforcement, national security, anti-terrorism or other issues that are related to public security.
    *   Other Parties in Connection with Corporate Transactions: We may disclose your information to a third party as part of a merger or transfer, acquisition or sale, or in the event of a bankruptcy.
    
    **HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SECURE?**
    
    We take data protection seriously. We have put in place physical and technical safeguards to keep the information we collect secure. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, Internet transmission, computer system, or wireless connection is completely secure.
    
    **WHERE DO WE SEND YOUR DATA?**
    
    Your use of our E-Commerce Platform will involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information within and outside of your country of residence consistent with this policy. In particular, your personal information will be transferred to the Republic of Korea. Please note that the data protection and other laws of countries to which your information may be transferred might not be as comprehensive as those in your country.
    
    In addition, your use of the Services may also involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information to other countries; such countries include, without limitation, countries in the European Economic Area, the United States of America, Brazil and India. We will take appropriate measures, in compliance with applicable law, to ensure that your personal information remains protected. Such measures include the use of Standard Contractual Clauses to safeguard the transfer of data outside of the EEA. To request more information, or to obtain a copy of the contractual agreements in place, please see our contact details below in the [**CONTACT US**](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section
    
    **WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?**
    
    Your personal information belongs to you. You can ask us to provide details about what we’ve collected, and you can ask us to delete it or correct any inaccuracies. You can also ask us to restrict or limit processing, sharing, or transfer of your personal information, as well as providing your personal information that we have collected to you so you can use it for your own purposes. We will not delete data that we are required by law to retain.
    
    To make a request concerning your rights or to make an enquiry, contact us as specified in the [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section.
    
    **HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**
    
    We will not keep your personal information for longer than is necessary for the purpose it was collected. This means that information will be destroyed or erased from our systems when it is no longer required.
    
    We take appropriate steps to ensure that we process and retain information about you based on the following logic:
    
    1.  at least the duration for which the information is used to provide you with a service;
    2.  as required under law, a contract, or with regard to our statutory obligations; or
    3.  only for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, is processed, or longer if required under any contract, by applicable law, or for statistical purposes, subject to appropriate safeguards.
    
    **WHAT THIRD PARTY SERVICES DO WE USE?**
    
    Some of the additional services such as online payments and credit services, content, advertising, and functionality in our services are provided by third parties. These third parties may also use cookies, beacons, tracking pixels, and other tools to collect information about your use of their and/or our services. These third parties are not controlled directly by Samsung, so we recommend that you check their privacy policies and/or terms and conditions to understand how they use your data and provide services.
    
    For some apps and services, including social networks, we receive and store sign-in information, as well as other information that you allow us to receive when you connect with these apps and services.
    
    **COOKIES, BEACONS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**
    
    We, as well as certain third parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality on our Services, use cookies, pixels, beacons, and other technologies in certain areas of our services, as explained in more detail below.
    
    Cookies
    
    Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, TV, mobile phone, or other device. They enable the entity that put the cookie on your device to recognise you across different websites, services, devices, and/or browsing sessions. Cookies serve many useful purposes. For example:
    
    *   Cookies can remember your sign-in credentials so you don’t have to enter those credentials each time you log on to a service.
    *   Cookies help us and third parties understand which parts of our services are the most popular because they help us to see which pages and features visitors are accessing and how much time they are spending on the pages. By studying this kind of information, we are better able to adapt the services and provide you with a better experience.
    *   Cookies help us and third parties understand which ads you have seen so that you don’t receive the same ad each time you access a service.
    *   Cookies help us and third parties provide you with relevant content and advertising by collecting information about your use of our services and other websites and apps.
    When you use a web browser to access the services, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. The operating system of your device may contain additional controls for cookies. Please note, however, that some services may be designed to work using cookies and that disabling cookies may affect your ability to use those services, or certain parts of them. We use the following types of cookies on our website:
    
    Essential Cookies
    
    These enable you to order products and receive services from our website;
    
    Performance Cookies
    
    Theses enable us to analyse the performance and design of our website and detect errors. For example, this type of cookie allows us to recognise that you have visited our website before and shows which sections of our website are most popular by allowing us to see which pages visitors access most frequently and how much time visitors spend on each page. We use, without limitation, Google Analytics, Adobe, and similar analytics cookies to achieve this. For example, the information generated by the cookie about the use of the website will normally be stored on a Google server in the United States. However, if you are located within the EU or the European Economic Area, your IP address will be shortened by Google beforehand. In exceptional cases only, your full address will be transmitted to a Google server in the United States and shortened there. On our behalf, Google will use this information for the purpose of compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP address transmitted from your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may prevent web usage data (including your IP address) generated by the cookie from being transmitted to Google and processed there if you download and install this Browser-Plugin ([http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)).
    
    Functional Cookies
    
    which allow us to deliver a better user experience. For example, this type of cookie ensures that the information displayed on your next visit to our website will match up with your user preferences, or your Samsung account from which you linked to our website, or the fact that you linked to our website via an email sent to you by Samsung or one of our trusted third party service providers contacting you on our behalf.
    
    Advertising Cookies
    
    which enables us and our carefully selected partners to deliver advertisements to you, or contact you directly where you have separately consented to such communications, which match your interests by, for example, collecting information about products you have browsed or ordered on our website. For example, and without limitation, we use Google remarketing tags to allow our retail partners to advertise products which you have browsed on our website. For further information about how Google remarketing tags work, please click here: [http://www.google.co.uk/think/products/newremarketing-tag.html](http://www.google.co.uk/think/products/newremarketing-tag.html). Our website may also display content from a third party website or service, which may result in cookies from third parties being stored on your hard drive or browser. We do not control the storage of these cookies and you should refer to the privacy policies of the relevant third party for more information.
    
    Other Local Storage
    
    We, along with certain third parties, may use other kinds of local storage technologies, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as “Flash cookies”) and HTML5 local storage, in connection with our services. These technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your device and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these technologies may make use of different parts of your device from standard cookies, and so you might not be able to control them using standard browser tools and settings. For information about disabling or deleting information contained in Flash cookies, please click here [http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html).
    
    Beacons and/or Pixels
    
    We, along with certain third parties, may also use technologies called beacons or pixels that communicate information from your device to a server. Beacons and pixels can be embedded in online content, videos, and emails, and can allow a server to read certain types of information from your device, know when you have viewed particular content or a particular email message, determine the time and date on which you viewed the beacon and pixels, and the IP address of your device. We and certain third parties use beacons and pixels for a variety of purposes, including to analyse the use of our Services and (in conjunction with cookies) to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you.
    
    When you access and use our Services (except for websites provided by third party service providers), you will be asked to provide your separate consent to the storage of cookies (which includes other local storage technologies, beacons, pixels and other information on your devices) by us. You will also be asked to provide your separate consent to the access of such cookies (which includes local storage technologies, beacons, pixels and information) by us and by the third parties mentioned above. Your experience of our website/services may be affected if you do not accept cookies, and further information will be provided to you at the time we ask you for this specific consent.
    
    **CONTACT US**
    
    You can contact us to update your preferences, correct your information, submit a request or ask us questions.
    
    Data Controller
    
    Samsung Electronics (UK) Limited
    
    Samsung House, 1000 Hillswood Drive, Chertsey, Surrey KT16 0PS
    
    Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.
    
    129, Samsung-ro, Yeongtong-gu,
    
    Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do 16677, Korea
    
    If you have any specific questions, please contact us at:
    
    European Data Protection Officer
    
    Samsung Electronics (UK) Limited
    
    Samsung House, 1000 Hillswood Drive, Chertsey, Surrey KT16 0PS
    
    You can also contact us by visiting our [Privacy Support Page](https://www.samsung.com/request-desk/). We are a global company with offices across Europe. This means that we will ensure your request or query is dealt with by the data protection team based in your region.
    
    You may lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes applicable law. Contact details for all EU Supervisory Authorities can be found [here](http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).
    
*   ### [SAMSUNG PRIVACY POLICY – SMART TV SUPPLEMENT](javascript:void(0))
    
    Samsung’s Smart TV service offers a set of features that provide enhanced video content, customized TV experiences, movies, connections to social networking services, and the ability to control and interact with your Smart TV with voice commands. We collect, use, share, and store information through your Smart TV and the devices connected with your Smart TV in the ways described in the Samsung Privacy Policy. This Supplement provides additional details about the privacy practices of some Smart TV features.
    
    The Smart TV is designed to enable you to easily find and access video programming and other content. For example, you may access information about live television programs distributed to you by your cable or satellite operator and on-demand video content offerings distributed by third party content providers through searchable guides displayed on your Smart TV.
    
    In the case of live television programs, we determine what content is available to you based in part on your postcode. Below, we provide information about additional services and features available on the Smart TV, namely: Viewing Information Services, Interest-Based Advertisements, and Voice Recognition. Further below, you will find the privacy notices related to each of these.
    
    _Viewing Information Services_
    
    In order to provide you with customized content on your Smart TV and highlight programming that is likely to interest you, Samsung may rely on your TV viewing history and Smart TV usage information to provide Viewing Information Services. This is an optional service that you may choose to activate to receive content and recommendations that are customized to your interests and entertainment preferences. If you choose not to activate this service, or to subsequently deactivate it, then you will receive generic content that is not customized to your specific interests or preferences and is based on your Smart TV usage information only. Smart TV usage information includes information about frequently launched apps, and the start and end time for launching and using apps.
    
    If you have activated Viewing Information Services, we base content and programming recommendations and additional services on:
    
    *   Information about content that you have watched, purchased, downloaded, or streamed through Samsung applications on your Smart TV or other devices;
    *   Information about applications you have accessed through the Smart TV;
    *   Information about your clicks on the “Like”, “Dislike”, “Watch Now”, and other buttons on your Smart TV;
    *   The query terms you enter into Smart TV search features, including when you search for particular video content;
    *   Other Smart TV device information, including, but not limited to, IP address, log data, information that identifies your hardware or software configuration, browser information, and the page(s) you request.
    
    For more detailed information about the Viewing Information Services, please refer to the Viewing Information Services Privacy Notice at the end of this Supplement.
    
    _Interest-Based Advertisements_
    
    Interest-Based Advertisements are designed to provide users with useful, interactive, and relevant advertisements about products and services offered by Samsung and third parties on your Samsung Smart TV or across various Samsung and third party platforms or devices, including linear commercials, on the web, mobile devices, and tablets.
    
    In order to make the advertisements on your devices more relevant to you, we may (in accordance with applicable law) rely on your TV viewing history (including information about the networks, channels, websites visited, and programs viewed on your Samsung Smart TV and the amount of time spent viewing them), Samsung Smart TV usage information, and other statistical data obtained from trusted third party data sources. We may use automatic content recognition (ACR) and other technologies to capture your TV viewing history.
    
    Based on the information above we create groups of Samsung Smart TV owners who share similar interests and use these categories of user groups for Interest-Based Advertisements. The information above is used to determine the groups to which your Samsung Smart TV is assigned and as a result, which advertisements your Smart TV and other connected devices receive.
    
    Interest-Based Advertisements is an optional feature, and you may choose to enable or disable it at any time by visiting the Settings menu on your Samsung Smart TV.
    
    Please note that your privacy choice with respect to the IBA Service will not affect whether or not you receive or are served with other types of ads and marketing that are not specifically based on TV viewing history or Samsung Smart TV usage information. Those other types of ads and marketing will be based on other information such as generalized location and other estimated or inferred information (e.g., IP address, and estimated TV size based on Model ID). Samsung processes this limited data – together with the Personalized Service ID (“PSID”) and Tizen ID for Advertising (“TIFA”) associated with your Smart TV – on the basis of its legitimate interest to serve generalized advertisements. These generalized advertisements might be less relevant because they are not based on your interests.
    
    For more detailed information about Interest-Based Advertisements, please refer to the Interest-Based Advertisements Privacy Notice at the end of this Supplement.
    
    _Voice Recognition_
    
    You can control your Smart TV, and use many of its features, with voice commands.
    
    If you enable Voice Recognition, you can interact with your Smart TV using your voice. To provide the Voice Recognition feature, your voice commands will be transmitted (along with information about your device, including device identifiers) to us and we will convert your voice commands into text to provide the Voice Recognition features. In addition, Samsung may collect voice commands and associated texts so that we can evaluate and improve the features. Samsung will collect your voice commands when you make a specific request to the Smart TV by clicking the activation button either on the remote control or on your screen or by speaking a wake word (e.g. “Hi, Bixby”) and speaking into the microphone on the remote control or Smart TV.
    
    If you do not enable Voice Recognition, you will not be able to use the voice recognition features.
    
    You may disable Voice Recognition data collection at any time by visiting the Settings menu. However, this would prevent you from using the Voice Recognition features.
    
    For more detailed information about the Voice Recognition, please refer to the Voice Recognition Privacy Notice at the end of this Supplement.
    
    _Third Parties_
    
    Please note that when you watch a video or access applications or content provided by a third party, that provider may collect or receive information about your Smart TV (e.g. its IP address and device identifiers), the requested transaction (e.g. your request to buy or rent the video), and your use of the application or service. Samsung is not responsible for these providers’ privacy or security practices. You should exercise caution and review the privacy statements applicable to the third party websites and services you use.
    
    _Country-Specific Features_
    
    Please note that one or more of the features described in this Smart TV Supplement may not be available to you depending on where you live.
    
*   ### [VIEWING INFORMATION SERVICES PRIVACY NOTICE](javascript:void(0))
    
    _Effective Date: 26th October, 2020_
    
    Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., and its affiliated companies (collectively “Samsung”) respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Notice applies to the personal information we may collect and use to provide customized content your Smart TV.
    
    This Privacy Notice provides information about how Samsung collects, uses and shares your personal information in connection with Viewing Information Services. Our Privacy Policy at https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp (“Samsung Privacy Policy”) will also apply to your use of Viewing Information Services, and should be read in conjunction with this Privacy Notice.
    
    **WHAT ARE VIEWING INFORMATION SERVICES?**
    
    In order to provide you with customized content on your Smart TV, Samsung may rely on your TV viewing history and Smart TV usage information. Smart TV usage information includes information about frequently launched apps, and the start and end time for launching and using apps. Viewing Information Services is an optional service that you may choose to activate to receive content that is customized to your interests and entertainment preferences. If you choose not to activate this service, or to subsequently deactivate it, then you will receive generic content that is not customized to your specific interests or preferences and is based on your Smart TV usage information only.
    
    **WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**
    
    We collect your TV viewing history, together with TV device identifiers (including Personalized Service ID or “PSID”) and IP address. Your TV viewing history includes information about:
    
    *   the networks, channels, websites visited and programs viewed on your Smart TV; and
    *   the amount of time spent viewing them.
    
    We may use automatic content recognition (ACR) and other technologies to capture this information. We collect this information when your Smart TV transfers video snippets or TV tuner information to our servers in order to determine the programs watched. When you consent to Viewing Information Services, then ACR will allow our Smart TVs to generate a unique video signature of TV frames in order to determine whether the video signature is from a TV program, Video-On-Demand titles, linear TV ads or video games. ACR does not identify content played through Samsung Smart TV apps.
    
    **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**
    
    We use the information described above to provide you customized content recommendations on your Smart TV, based on your interests and entertainment preferences.
    
    Samsung processes personal information for Viewing Information Services on the basis of your consent, which you may provide by affirmatively ticking the checkbox associated with this Privacy Notice. You may subsequently withdraw your consent at any time by visiting the Settings menu (or by accessing the Privacy Choices app, if this is available on your Smart TV), in which case your TV viewing history will cease to be processed for that particular feature or purpose.
    
    **WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?**
    
    We will share your personal information internally within our business, and with other Samsung Electronics Group companies which we control and/or own, for the purpose of providing Viewing Information Services.
    
    **WHERE DO WE SEND YOUR DATA?**
    
    Your use of our Services will involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information within and outside of your country of residence, consistent with this policy. In particular, your personal information will be transferred to the Republic of Korea. Please note that the data protection and other laws of countries to which your information may be transferred might not be as comprehensive as those in your country.
    
    \[For European Economic Area (EEA) Residents Only\]
    
    In addition, your use of the Services may also involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information to other countries; such countries include, without limitation, countries in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, the United States of America, Canada, and India. We will take appropriate measures, in compliance with applicable law, to ensure that your personal information remains protected. Such measures include the use of Standard Contractual Clauses to safeguard the transfer of data outside of the EEA. To request more information or to obtain a copy of the contractual agreements in place, contact us. See the [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section.
    
    **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**
    
    Please refer to the following sections of the Samsung Privacy Policy for more information:

    **UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE**
    
    This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our personal information practices with respect to Viewing Information Services or changes in the applicable law. We will post a notice on our website and/or your device to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Notice, and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.
    
*   ### [INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISEMENTS PRIVACY NOTICE](javascript:void(0))
    
    _Effective Date: 26th October, 2020_
    
    Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd (‘Samsung’) and its affiliated companies respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Notice applies to the personal information we collect and use to display interest-based advertisements on your Smart TV and other connected devices.
    
    This Privacy Notice should be read in conjunction with the Samsung Privacy Policy, which applies to your general use of the Samsung Smart TV and can be found at [https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp](https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp).
    
    In this Privacy Notice, we describe the types of personal information used for interest-based advertisements, how we use that information, and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information and exercising your rights. Samsung is the data controller for the processing of personal information to display interest-based advertisements as described in this Privacy Notice.
    
    **WHAT ARE INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISEMENTS?**
    
    Interest-based advertisements are designed to provide users with useful, interactive, and relevant advertisements about products and services offered by Samsung and third parties on your Samsung Smart TV or across various Samsung and third-party platforms or devices, including linear commercials, on the web, mobile devices, and tablets.
    
    In order to make the advertisements on your devices more relevant to you, we may—with your consent—analyze your TV viewing history (including information about the networks, channels, websites visited, and programs viewed on your Samsung Smart TV and the amount of time spent viewing them), Samsung Smart TV usage information, and other statistical data obtained from trusted third-party data sources. We may use automatic content recognition (“ACR”) and other technologies to capture and analyze your TV viewing history when you enable Viewing Information Services on your Samsung Smart TV. For more information on the Viewing Information Services feature, please select “Read More” in the where it appears beside the Viewing Information Services tick box.
    
    Based on the information above, we create groups of Samsung Smart TV users who share similar interests and use these categories of user groups for interest-based advertisements. The information above is used to determine the groups to which your Samsung Smart TV is assigned and as a result, which advertisements your Smart TV and other connected devices receive.
    
    Please note that some third parties may display interest-based advertisements in their apps on your Samsung Smart TV. These third parties are responsible for their own data practices, for example to have a valid legal basis to process your personal data. If you want to know how these third parties process your personal data, please review the privacy policies for their platforms and apps.
    
    To further protect your privacy, Samsung also provides you with additional options to exercise control over interest-based advertisements on third parties’ apps. For example, third parties are disallowed from processing your data to display interest-based advertisements in their apps unless they have both a valid legal basis for it on their own app and you have also opted in to interest-based advertisements on the Samsung Smart TV. If you would like to learn more about these options, please see the [PSID AND TIFA](#psid-and-tifa) and [YOUR CHOICES](#your-choices) sections below or visit www.samsungtifa.com for more information.
    
    **WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**
    
    To provide you with interest-based advertisements, we may obtain the following information about your devices, which may include personal information:
    
    *   Device Information. We collect information such as your device model, operating system versions, device configurations and settings, IP address, and device identifiers (including the Personalized Service ID (“PSID”) and Tizen ID For Advertising (“TIFA”), which are unique, randomized, and user-resettable identifiers associated with your Smart TV, as described further below).
    *   Device Usage and Log Information. We collect information about how, when, and for how long you use your devices, including your interactions with interest-based advertisements and Samsung and third-party apps and services on the devices (such as a listing of apps on your devices).
    *   TV Viewing Information. We collect your TV viewing history. Your TV viewing history includes information about the networks, channels, websites visited, and programs viewed on your Samsung Smart TV and the amount of time spent viewing them. We may use ACR and other technologies to capture and analyze this TV viewing history when you enable the Viewing Information Services on your Samsung Smart TV (as described in the Viewing Information Services privacy notice).
    *   Statistical Information. We may use statistical information about you or your devices such as generalized location and estimated age group. We obtain this statistical information from commercially available sources (as permitted by law) such as our third-party service providers. We only work with third-party service providers who ensure that this information has been obtained in accordance with applicable law and can be provided to us for use and disclosure.
    
    _PSID AND TIFA_
    
    Information about your device usage that is collected for the purposes of providing interest-based advertisements will be linked to a randomized, non-persistent, and resettable device identifier called the PSID. We will use the PSID for the display of advertisements to Samsung Smart TV users. You may reset your PSID as specified in the [YOUR CHOICES](#your-choices) section of this Privacy Notice.
    
    In order to protect your personal information and your preferences, third parties intending to provide advertisements in their apps will do so by collecting and using the TIFA associated with your Samsung Smart TV. The TIFA is a randomized version of your device's PSID, and this randomization ensures that such third parties do not know that it is your specific device to which advertisements are sent. Please visit www.samsungtifa.com if you would like to learn more about interest-based advertisements offered by third parties.
    
    **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**
    
    We use the information described above to:
    
    *   display (and allow advertisers to display) interest-based advertising on your Smart TV and other connected devices; and
    *   improve and customize your experience with interest-based advertisements.
    
    Samsung processes personal information for interest-based advertisements on the basis of your consent, which you may provide by affirmatively selecting the tick box associated with this privacy notice. You may subsequently withdraw your consent at any time by accessing the Privacy Choices App or in the Settings on the Smart TV without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
    
    **WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?**
    
    We may share your information:
    
    *   internally, with other Samsung Electronics Group companies, for example, AdGear Technologies Inc. which we control and/or own, for the purpose of providing interest-based advertisements to you;
    *   with our service providers, who assist us in providing interest-based advertising; and
    *   externally, we may share certain information – such as IP address, TIFA, ad placement information (e.g., screen resolution), and consent opt-in/out status – with ad platforms, and other advertising partners to enable them to provide interest-based advertisements (if you have opted in) or generalized advertisements (if you have opted out).
    
    **WHERE DO WE SEND YOUR DATA?**
    
    Your use of our Services will involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information within and outside of your country of residence, consistent with this policy. In particular, your personal information will be transferred to the Republic of Korea. Please note that the data protection and other laws of countries to which your information may be transferred might not be as comprehensive as those in your country.
    
    \[For European Economic Area (EEA) Residents Only
    
    In addition, your use of the Services may also involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information to other countries; such countries include, without limitation, countries in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, the United States of America, Canada, and India. We will take appropriate measures, in compliance with applicable law, to ensure that your personal information remains protected. Such measures include the use of Standard Contractual Clauses to safeguard the transfer of data outside of the EEA. To request more information or to obtain a copy of the contractual agreements in place, contact us. See the [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section.
    
    **YOUR CHOICES**
    
    We offer you certain choices in connection with your personal information collected and used by us and/or third parties for purposes of interest-based advertisements.
    
    You may reset your [PSID AND TIFA](#psid-and-tifa) at any time by selecting “Reset PSID” on the settings menu, and once reset, your TV viewing history and Smart TV usage information will not be linked to the its previous PSID (or TIFA). Bear in mind that if you reset your PSID, the quality of interest-based advertisements will be affected.
    
    In addition, you may disable interest-based advertisements at any time by accessing the Privacy Choices app or the Settings menu on the Smart TV
    
    If you withdraw from interest-based advertisements, you will no longer receive interest-based advertisements provided by us and the third parties. Please note, however, that your privacy choice with respect to interest-based advertisements will not affect whether or not you receive or are served with other types of ads and marketing that are not specifically based on TV viewing history or Samsung Smart TV usage information. Those other types of ads and marketing will be based on other information such as generalized location and other estimated or inferred information (e.g., estimated TV size based on Model ID). They might be less relevant because they are not based on your interests. Samsung processes this limited personal data to serve generalized advertisements on the Smart TV that are not based on users’ viewing behavior or other specific interests.
    
    **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**
    
    Please refer to the following sections of the Samsung Privacy Policy for more information:

    **UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE**
    
    This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our personal information practices with respect to interest-based advertisements or changes in the applicable law. We will post a notice on our website and/or your device to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Notice, and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.
    
*   ### [VOICE RECOGNITION SERVICE PRIVACY NOTICE](javascript:void(0))
    
    Effective Date: 1st March, 2019
    
    Samsung Electronics and its affiliated companies respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Notice applies to the personal information we collect through the Voice Recognition service (the “Voice Service”).
    
    The Voice Service is a service that provides capabilities for users to find and watch content and manage their world across the Samsung products using only their voice. Its features include the natural language processing in content search and their Samsung Smart TV control; Internet, weather, and other services users have come to expect from their Samsung Smart TVs.
    
    Depending on the language you select, you may use and enjoy the enhanced voice recognition feature, Bixby. When Bixby is activated you may acknowledge it by the icons, banners, or other marks on your Samsung Smart TV screen.
    
    This Privacy Notice provides further, specific information about how your personal information is used in connection with the Voice Service, and should be read in conjunction with the Samsung Privacy Policy, which also applies to your receipt of the Voice Service and can be found at [https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp](https://account.samsung.com/membership/pp).
    
    In this Privacy Notice, we describe the types of information collected through the Voice Service, how we may use the information and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information. Samsung is the data controller for the processing of personal information.
    
    _WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?_
    
    Through the Voice Service, we may obtain information about you in various ways. The types of personal information we obtain include:
    
    *   Samsung account Information (Optional). When you log in to Samsung account on your Smart TV, we may collect information associated with your Samsung account used to access the Voice Service, such as your name, email address, and Samsung account ID.
    *   The Voice Service Interactions. We may collect information you exchange with the Voice Service through your interactions with the Services, including recordings of your voice commands (such as your questions, requests, and instructions), your pictures, and other inputs, and the information you receive from the Services (such as responses, answers, and content). We also may obtain other information related to your use of the Voice Service, including the information (such as information related to the apps you use, the websites you visit, and pictures, music, calendar entries, bookmarks, and content and data from other Samsung and third party apps, websites, and services) we receive from Samsung and third party apps and services that are accessed or used by the Voice Service to provide you with the Services (such as music streaming and weather).
    *   Geolocation Data. We may receive your device’s geolocation and other information related to your location through postcode information stored on the TV which can be obtained through your IP address or through your input for certain purposes, such as to provide you with the Services.
    *   Device and App Information. We may collect information through automated means about your Voice Service-enabled devices, such as device models, OS versions, device configurations and settings, IP addresses, and device identifiers and other unique identifiers. In addition, we may obtain information about how, when, and for how long you use your Voice Service-enabled devices, including your usage of the Voice Service and Samsung and third party apps and services on the devices (such as a list of apps on your devices, music played on your devices, the websites you visit, and the searches you make).
    
    _HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?_
    
    We may use the information we obtain through the Voice Service to:
    
    *   provide you with the Services, such as to respond to your requests, questions, and instructions made through the Voice Service;
    *   identify and authenticate you so you may use the Voice Service;
    *   improve and customize your experience with the Voice Service, such as delivering content and responses tailored to our users and the manner in which they interact with the Voice Service;
    *   with your separate consent, communicate with you about our products and services, and provide you with notifications, content, alerts, offers, promotions, marketing information, communications, and advertisements;
    *   respond to your requests and enquiries;
    *   operate, evaluate, and improve our business (including developing new products; enhancing and improving our products and services; managing our communications; analyzing our products, customer base and services; conducting market research; performing data analytics; and performing accounting, auditing, and other internal functions);
    *   allow you to interact with and use certain third party apps and services;
    *   protect against, identify, and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims, and other liabilities; and
    *   comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards, and our policies, including this Privacy Notice, the Samsung account Privacy Policy.
    
    Through the Voice Service, we may collect personal information about your online activities on Voice Service-enabled devices over time and across third party apps, websites, and other online services. We may use third party analytics services on our Services. The providers that administer these analytics services help us analyse your use of the Services and improve our Services. The information we obtain may be disclosed to or collected directly by these providers and other relevant third parties who use the information, for example, to evaluate use of the Services, help provide the Services, and diagnose technical issues.
    
    Samsung processes personal information for the purposes described above. Samsung’s legal basis to process personal information includes processing that is: necessary for the performance of the contract between you and Samsung (for example, to provide you with the Services and to identify and authenticate you so you may use certain Services); necessary to comply with legal requirements (for example, to comply with applicable accounting rules and to make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement); necessary for Samsung’s legitimate interests (for example, to manage our relationship with you and to improve the Services); and based on consent by our customers (for example, to communicate with you about our products and services and provide you with marketing information), which may subsequently be withdrawn at any time by contacting us as specified in the Contact Us section of Samsung Privacy Policy without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
    
    You are required, as a necessity to enter into a contract, to provide us with personal information for processing as described above. If you do not provide us with personal information, we will not be able to provide you all of the features available through the Voice Service.
    
    _YOUR CHOICES_
    
    You may disable the Voice Service at any time by visiting the Settings menu, however this may prevent you from using the Voice Service.
    
    And also, we offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information we obtain about you. To update your preferences, limit the communications you receive from us, or submit a request, please contact us as specified in the How to [CONTACT US](#privacy-ctns-eleven) section of Samsung Privacy Policy
    
    _UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE_
    
    This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our personal information practices with respect to the Services or changes in the applicable law. We will post a notice on our website and/or your device to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Notice and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.

**Product & Service** [open](javascript:void(0);)

**Support** [open](javascript:void(0);)

**Company** [open](javascript:void(0);)

**Company** [open](javascript:void(0);)

Copyright© 1995-2020 Samsung. All rights reserved.

This website is best viewed using Internet Explorer 11 or higher, the latest version of Chrome or Firefox browsers.

STAY IN THE LOOP?

Go to Top
